Good news, everyone.
Several years ago,
I tried to log on to AOL,
and it just went through. Whee!
We're online.
Go ahead, get into these net suits.
I designed and tested them myself.
They smell like
burning rhesus monkey.
Really? I guess
when you're around it all day
you stop noticing.
Off you go.
Hey.
Ha!
Behold!
The Internet!
My god.
It's full of ads.
Follow me.
It's immense.
It's got every piece of information
anyone could ever want.
So I see.
- Woo-hoo!
- Oh, yeah!
What? What's going on here?
Hey, that's me.
No, it isn't.
I just took some pictures of your face
and stuck them on someone else's body.
Hey.
Are you over 18?
- Yes.
Hi.
I'm telling you, Fry,
they've got a chat room for everybody.
And here it is.
- Ew. That is so gross.
- Yeah.
- I'll stick with this one, thank you.
Hi.
I'm a naughty nurse
and I really need someone to talk to.
$9.95 a minute.
Oh! You're a dollar naughtier than most.
So, how about them knicks?
Hello? Are there any girls
in this room at all?
Yeah. Bring on the hot chicks
'cause I'm a hot stud.
- Yeah.
- So are we.
I'm a woman
if that's what you mean.
It's a girl.
I don't like to play games,
so I'll just say I'm a cyclops.
I'm a spaceship captain.
I'm the only one of my species.
And I'm interested in meeting a man.
A woman?
I'm scared.
Well, thanks to the Internet,
I'm now bored with sex.
Is there a place on the web that
panders to my lust for violence?
Is the space pope reptilian?
Get ready for fun, Fry.
Nowadays we have a type of game
played entirely on video.
We call it a video game.
Uh, a video game, you say?
Well, golly gee.
You mighty spacemen of the future
will have to show me how it works.
Hmm.
The doctor is in.
The doctor is out.
Everyone, please sign off.
We have a delivery.
Plus I have to use the phone to...
Leela, please tell the others that...
Who are you?
I saw you in the chat room
But you left before I had
a chance to talk to you.
After all these years of
searching for another cyclops.
I can't believe it.
I've dreamed of this moment all my life.
Do you think perhaps, you and I...
Ha-ha!
Fry, you idiot.
Ever since I was abandoned on Earth
I've been searching for who my people are
and where they come from.
Then I finally meet another cyclops
and you blast him.
You wrecked my one chance
to learn who I am.
Oh, Leela, I feel terrible.
If there's anything I can ever do...
Gotcha.
I won!
I'm the greatest!
Come on. We have work to do.
Are you still mad at me for wrecking
your once-in-a-lifetime chance
to learn the meaning of your existence?
No. I'm just happy you were able
to win a video game.
Now let's concentrate on getting
this desperately needed popcorn
to the people of Cineplex 14, okay?
Leela, you've got mail.
It's not spam.
Huh?
It's him.
To Leela.
Subject, hello. I am Alcazar.
Fortunately, I wrote down your screen name
before I was dispatched
by that oafish moron.
Kicked your ass.
Leela, we have much to discuss.
Please come join me
on the planet of your birth.
Coordinates follow.
Well, too bad we've got
to make that urgent popcorn delivery.
It'll get there.
After a whole life of searching,
I may finally have found where I belong.
Too bad it's a dump.
Look at that statue.
It's only got one eye.
Lazy sculptor.
Welcome home, Leela.
Alcazar?
Are you real or am I seeing single?
Ow.
Of course I'm real.
After all this time,
somebody else with one eye,
who isn't a clumsy carpenter
or a kid with a BB gun.
It's all right, Leela.
You'll never be alone again.
Come.
Let me introduce you to yourself.
- Do you mind if your servants walk?
- Not at all.
We are the last remaining cyclopes.
Our planet is Cyclopia.
This is the capital, Cyclops City.
Stop me if I'm too fast for you.
So much information, and yet, somehow
I feel as if I know it all already.
This sacred mosaic
depicts our goddess of beauty.
Hmm. You got any
sacred artwork of her from the back?
Her perfect eye
reminds me of yours, Leela.
Had our race survived
you would have been a temple priestess
or a supermodel.
Oh, please. Really?
There's the infamous pirate, Purple beard,
scourge of the six seas.
What's over
that hill?
The Forbidden Valley.
A holy sanctuary
where no one may tread.
Is that anything like a cemetery?
'Cause I got to take a leak. Ow!
Fry, that's offensive to our people.
- Isn't it?
- Ow.
This is my home.
I hope you don't think less of me
because I live in a giant castle.
Oh, no, not at all.
If anything, I'm more impressed.
Ooh. I'm going to need
to make some room.
And here is where
I dream my lonely dreams
and cook my simple meals.
It's all so sad.
What happened to our people?
That's too painful to speak of now.
Come. I'll show you your quarters.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
I heard you from my room.
What's wrong?
Nothing. It's just...
No, Leela.
I don't want to see tears
in your perfect eye.
Please. Is it about the fate
of our people?
Because I'm very interested in that.
Well, okay. But it's chilly,
and you're going to be
all wet from the tears.
Let's go into my chamber.
It wasn't long ago,
our people were happy and prosperous.
But the eyeless mole people of Subterra 3
grew jealous of our visual prowess.
They fired missiles in all directions,
hoping to hit Cyclopia.
Unfortunately, one of
the 40 planets hit was ours.
How far away do you think it is?
A trillion miles?
Things got hot.
You look a little hot, actually.
You could take off that jacket.
Our people don't like to be hot.
Anyway, just before the impact,
our smartest scientist
managed to save one baby.
Alcazar, I used to be a baby.
It might have been me.
Fortunately, I was employed
as a pool cleaner at the time.
And when I emerged
from retrieving a dead possum
I found I was the only one left.
It's so tragic.
Yes, but the real tragedy
is that our race ends with us.
- It doesn't have to.
- What do you mean?
You're a male.
And I'm a female.
I'm still not following you.
Wake up, my king.
Geez, what a night.
Make me some coffee, would ya?
Uh, sure. Okay.
- What do you take with that?
- Pancakes and sausage.
Kitchen's in basement,
pans in attic.
Maybe after breakfast, we can talk about
rebuilding our civilization.
Mmm.
Great pancakes, Leela.
Yeah, they'll come in handy
if I need to cover any tiny manholes.
Listen, hon,
we don't want to look like slobs
- in front of the other species, do we?
- No.
So get to work on these dishes.
And then organize my collection
of naked celebrity photos.
- Look, Alcazar...
- Call me Al.
Look, Al.
I know you've been
living alone a long time,
and I can sympathize.
But I'm not your maid.
You're right. I'm sorry.
I guess the relationship
isn't going to work out.
So much for the cyclops race.
It was a pretty good race but...
Okay, okay.
I'll do the dishes.
Hey, where'd they go?
Leela is experiencing
the greatest joy a woman can feel,
worshipping some lowlife jerk.
He may be some lowlife jerk,
but I don't trust him.
I think he's hiding something,
and I'm going to find out what it is.
Try and stop me.
Al?
I did my hair the way you wanted it.
Who are these people?
Friends.
Hey, where'd you get this couch
and that TV set and all this stuff?
They were giving it away
on the street corner.
Just like you, Leela.
Too bad they weren't giving away
the three things you actually need,
mouthwash, a back wax,
and stain-proof underwear.
You go, girl!
By the way, your pal Fry
fell into the dungeon.
Take him a taco so
he doesn't die and stink up the place.
Come on, Al.
Can't you let the little guy out?
Geez, Leela, twice in one day?
I'm not Superman.
Why were you sneaking
into my people's Forbidden Valley?
'Cause I think Alcazar's
hiding something from you.
Listen, Leela, you may not like it.
You may not believe it or want to hear it.
But Alcazar's a jerk.
He's bad for you. He...
- I know.
- You do?
Fry, if it's obvious to you
with your learning disability
then, of course, it's obvious to me.
He's crude and gross,
and he treats me like a slave.
Then dump his one-eyed ass.
I can't.
If I leave Alcazar
that's the end of the cyclops race.
And I won't let that happen,
even if it means
a lifetime of unhappiness.
Leela, mop up in aisle number two.
I'll break up with him at dinner.
I'll be there.
Yo, Leela, what gives?
Pig says your slop tastes like crap.
Yeah, like crap.
Come on, Leela.
You deserve better than this guy.
Dump him already.
I'm trying.
Hey, everyone,
jam a sock in your spit faucets.
Not long ago, I spent my lonely nights
renting slasher flicks
with Ratman and his girlfriend.
But then a beautiful woman arrived...
Stop eating, Pig!
...and she brought new hope for me
and our once-great civilization.
Now, a million centuries
of cyclops destiny
depend on the answer
to one question.
Leela, will you marry me?
No. No.
Yes, I will!
Oh!
They're getting married.
Congratulations, Leela.
- Glad you could make it.
- It's a magical day.
Welcome!
Psst, Leela!
You've got to get me out of here.
It's horrible. Eating scraps,
letting my waste drop wherever it falls
like an animal in a zoo.
Animals go in the corner.
The corner. Why didn't I think of that?
Look, Fry, I'd like to help you
but it's my wedding, and I'm kind of busy.
Here. Try to be happy for me.
That way, at least one of us will be.
That's it.
It's time for this bird to walk.
Ow!
Bender! Come on, we've got to
get some dirt on Alcazar.
Let's go find out what makes the
Forbidden Valley so forbidden.
Uh, no thanks. I'm good.
But there's probably some cool
forbidden stuff you can steal.
I don't know, Fry.
For the first time in my life, I feel like
I've stolen enough.
Bender, snap out of it.
Sorry. I don't know
what came over me.
Let's go!
I love stealin'
I love takin' things
That pig over there is wearing
the same sandals as me.
Come on, boy, jump!
Good boy.
Whoa, mittens.
My god!
Four identical castles.
Each more identical than the last.
That's weird. It's another cyclops.
Only this one has five eyes.
And here's another one with no eyes.
Does anyone have a reason
why this couple
shall not be joined
in the irrevocable shackles of holy bliss?
Saving a race of one-eyed monsters?
Who could object to that?
Cut to the chase, preach.
Do you, Alcazar, take this woman...
...in sickness, to love, death, part?
Yeah, sure, I do. Come on, faster!
Do you, Leela,
copy and paste his response
till death do you part?
I...
Oh, my god.
- What the...
- Hey, Alcazar,
you left somebody
off the guest list.
Alcazar!
Why you are so late
for our wedding?
And why you have only one eye?
It's...
Oh.
Uh... Hey, sweetie.
Just go back to the castle
and wait for me.
She... She's nuts.
I can morph into a five-eyed alien
and I kind of said I'd marry her.
But I'm really a cyclops
and I'm really going to marry you.
Oh, yeah?
Then what about this?
This is a bit awkward.
- Who's she?
Who are they?
Go back to the castle, Sandy.
And maybe you'd like to meet her
and her.
This...
Leela...
This must all be very confusing.
A little.
That's why I've decided to hurt you
until you explain it.
Show us your real form.
- Yeah!
- Do it!
Well, this is the real me,
but I can explain.
We all have needs.
Mine was to make it with five weirdos
and have them scrub my five castles.
I gave you all what you wanted
and, of course, I made
a few bucks
letting Pig watch
through the two-way mirror.
Can any of you say
you wouldn't have done
the exact same thing in my position?
He's a saint.
But why did you have all
five weddings on the same day?
Hey, lady, you got any idea what it costs
to rent a tux that changes shape?
All right, Alcazar.
- I just have one last question for you.
- What's that?
If you could change form
why didn't you change it
in the one place that counts?
Thanks for saving me
from that creep, Fry.
Hey, that's what I do.
I guess I was so desperate
to find out who I really was
I forgot who I really was.
No harm done.
In the many decades
you'll work to repay me
for that shipment of popcorn
you destroyed
you'll have plenty of time
to search for your true home.
Yeah.
I mean, how many planets
can there be?